-(Todo yelling)
-(punches thudding)
[Todo] When I was in third grade
I beat up a cocky
high school kid.
(kid groaning)
Even if he was older,
cocky is still cocky.
The kid was mockin' me!
(bird calling)
(hand scraping)
And when I feel mocked, well,
that's as good as a
starting bell in the ring!
It wasn't even that fun.
I found out that
trouncing a boring guy
was naturally boring too.
-(Todo sighing)
-(intense rock music)
[Yuki] Nice fight, boy!
[Todo] Huh?
So, when it comes to women,
what's your type?
What the?
Who are you?
(Yuki chuckling)
One look at her and I knew.
My boring world was about
to be flipped upside-down.
(opening theme music)
(singer singing in Japanese)
(air whistling)
The time to unleash my
technique has finally come!
Huh?
Didn't you use it before?
Look, in our current situation,
I don't have time to
explain my technique to you!
There's really only one
piece of advice I can give you.
Don't stop!
And believe in me!
Okay!
But that's two.
(pensive rock music)
[Todo] Let's examine the
cards our opponent's holding.
One is roots that
emerge from the ground.
That one probably
gains power and speed
the more it limits
quantity and range.
Then there's Wooden Ball.
Each ball can attack once or
twice and then it's expended.
They can remain airborne
and we have to watch
out for delayed activation.
Then there's Cursed Bud, that's
probably what got Fushiguro.
I guess you're out if even
if one of those hits you,
though I wanna
believe that means
it can't fire too many of them.
As for Flower Field, it
looks like that relaxes you,
but its earlier wounds
are throwing it off now,
so no need to worry about that.
Then there's that
unleashed left arm
and the possibility
it's just a bluff.
However, it doesn't
matter what a technique is
if you don't let
them activate it!
So even accounting for
unexpected situations,
(air whooshing)
my 530,000 IQ mental CPU
(text chiming)
(neurons crackling)
produces only one
inescapable conclusion:
victory!
-♪ Oh ♪
-♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
Because I'm not alone, brother!
Because you're here!
-♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
-(footsteps thundering)
And you're with me!
(root whipping)
Huh?
(Hanami scoffing)
(Todo yelling)
Todo!
(Yuji panting)
(Todo yelling)
-(Todo grunting)
-(Todo crashing)
(gasping) Todo!
-(Yuji grunting)
-(blows thudding)
(air whooshing)
[Hanami] That's one down.
(Todo clapping)
(blood splatting)
(Hanami gurgling)
(Yuji sputtering)
(air whooshing)
Whoa, Todo?
[Hanami] I see.
It's simple, and yet therefore
it's a troubling
technique you have.
Yes.
It's simply swapping my
position for that of my opponent's.
The Boogie Woogie!
(Yuji gasping)
-Todo- -Shh!
I will end this
before it can adapt.
(Todo chuckling)
(Todo growling)
(footsteps thundering)
By the way, (clapping)
clapping my hands (clapping)
is necessary to activate it!
(Todo clapping)
-(air whooshing)
-(footsteps thudding)
-(Yuji and Todo grunting)
-(blows thudding)
(Todo clapping)
-(Yuji and Todo grunting)
-(blows thudding)
(Todo clapping) [Hanami] Huh?
(Todo clapping)
-(Yuji grunting)
-(blows thudding)
-(Todo grunting)
(Hanami hissing)
Their builds are too different!
There's a big change
every time they swap!
(Todo clapping)
-(Yuji and Todo grunting)
-(blows thudding)
Is he swapping with me
or is he swapping
with Sukuna's vessel?
Every time he claps,
that split-second decision
makes my thoughts falter!
(Todo clapping)
(air whooshing)
-(Yuji grunting)
-(blow thudding)
(Hanami groaning)
Oh no!
I can't, I can't!
(Todo clapping)
(blow thudding)
-(Yuji grunting)
-(blow thudding)
-(Todo grunting)
-(blows thudding)
-(Yuji grunting)
-(blow thudding)
(Todo clapping)
-(Yuji and Todo grunting)
-(blows thudding)
(Hanami groaning)
(Todo clapping)
I can't break out of this!
-(Todo grunting)
-(blow thudding)
(Hanami yelping)
(air whooshing)
(Hanami gasping)
They're using that again!
Using Black Flash consecutively
isn't anything amazing.
(cup clinking)
(gentle pensive music)
Although I find it
is difficult, for me,
to do it more than twice in a
row or on the following day.
It doesn't matter if
the first one is landed
by skill or by a fluke, once
sorcerers land a Black Flash,
they temporarily enter a state
that athletes
commonly call the zone.
The manipulation
of cursed energy
that they normally
control consciously
then becomes as
natural as breathing,
and then there's a
sense of omnipotence
that makes it seem
as if everything else
revolves around them.
I guess that's how I'd put it.
You wanna know
what my record is?
(Nanami sighing)
Four times.
But really I just got lucky.
-(Yuji grunting)
-(intense rock music)
(blow booming)
[Yuji] Black Flash!
[Todo] Brother, I keep having
a premonition about you!
-(Hanami groaning)
-(energy crackling)
(Hanami screaming)
(air whooshing)
(blow crashing)
[Yuji] Black Flash!
-(Hanami groaning)
-(blood splatting)
(energy crackling)
Black Flash!
[Todo] Three in a row?
[Hanami] Don't get cocky!
-(air whooshing)
-(Hanami gasping)
Swapping positions?
So what I have to
watch out for now
(Todo clapping)
is Sukuna's vessel!
They didn't swap?
-(air whooshing)
-(energetic rock music)
Just 'cause I clap my hands
doesn't always mean I'm
activating my technique!
It's simple, but
it's easy to fall for.
I keep getting that
same premonition
of my boredom being
turned upside-down!
(blow crashing)
[Yuji] Black Flash!
(energetic music)
(discordant energetic music)
(leaves rustling)
(air whooshing)
(energetic pensive music)
(footsteps thundering)
-(Yuji grunting)
-(Wooden Ball shattering)
-(Todo grunting)
-(blows thudding)
(Todo clapping)
-(Yuji grunting)
-(blow thudding)
-Huh?
(roots booming)
♪ Sometimes I
might make you cry ♪
♪ Not on purpose ♪
(Hanami grunting)
(Todo clapping)
-(Todo grunting)
-(roots thudding)
(Yuji grunting)
-(blows thudding)
-(Yuji grunting)
[Yuji] It's attacking
before each swap!
It's getting used to Todo's
technique and adapting!
[Todo] Ah, but that
Black Flash hurt it!
We can exorcize it, together!
[Hanami] This is the first time
I've ever been hurt
so badly in a fight,
and yet, despite that,
(ground rumbling)
my delight in this
battle is only growing!
-(Cursed Buds chattering)
-(tense music)
(air whooshing)
-(Cursed Buds chattering)
-(Cursed Buds whooshing)
(Todo clapping)
(Yuji grunting)
(air whooshing)
His technique
reveal was full of lies!
Now it turns out he's able
to swap two others as well?
Todo!
He's protecting me!
[Todo] Don't worry, Brother!
By seriously hardening my
body and my cursed energy,
I'll easily repel these buds!
-(energy whooshing)
-(tense music)
(door rattling)
Huh?
Are you sure of that?
(pensive music)
(gasping) Ta...
Takada?
(dreamy chiming)
You remember Fushiguro's
injuries from those buds?
Of course I do!
In just a matter of seconds,
those same Cursed Buds
are gonna be
slamming right into me!
Then think, Fushiguro's
Buds had grown larger
by the time he
was rescued, right?
(Todo gasping)
You're assuming they
grew by absorbing his blood
and that is possible, of course,
but you're facing
a cursed spirit here.
So what's the
most likely answer?
(clock ticking)
(snapping) Cursed energy!
(text chiming)
(energy whooshing)
(Todo chuckling)
(Cursed Buds thudding)
(Hanami gasping)
[Hanami] He dispelled
his cursed energy!
And right before impact.
He must have figured it out.
The harder they defend
with cursed energy,
the stronger those Buds become!
Her next event is the national.
-(text chiming)
-(Todo grunting)
I'll have to be sure to
thank her then, yeah?
-(Yuji grunting)
-(blows thudding)
(Yuji grunting)
(Todo grunting)
-(blow crashing)
-(Hanami screaming)
♪ Should burn up ♪
Hey, special-grade
cursed spirit!
By now I'm sure you've realized
that I didn't tell you
everything before,
and now there's one more thing
you should be thinking about:
what counts as a target
for Boogie Woogie!
What things can I swap in
the range of my technique?
Only other creatures?
Mais non!
My technique works
on cursed corpses
and inanimate objects too!
So the answer is:
anything possessing cursed
energy above a certain level!
(Todo grunting)
Hey, special-grade cursed
spirit, have you noticed?
We're back at that spot again.
Which means this is
where it lies waiting!
(Todo clapping)
(chains rattling)
(Hanami gasping)
(air whooshing)
Look in the riverbed for
Maki's special-grade tool
The eye-trees on
its face are fragile.
-(energy booming)
-(Yuji grunting)
What the hell?
Whoa, did I just swap
places with a fish?
(chains rattling)
[Todo] Special-grade
cursed tool!
-(Todo yelling)
-(air whooshing)
(tool crashing)
Playful Cloud!
(blow booming)
(Hanami shouting)
-(Todo gasping)
-(roots booming)
(Todo grunting)
Even a blow from a
special-grade cursed tool
imbued with my cursed
energy didn't take it down?
Huh?
(energy warbling)
(plants crackling)
(Todo gasping)
[Hanami] Plants don't
generate cursed energy,
so I use my left arm to
steal the life from plants
and convert that life
into cursed energy,
(flower squelching)
but that never
gets returned to me,
and instead it all goes
to this flower offering.
I was hoping I wouldn't
have to use this.
(energy crackling)
(footsteps
thudding) [Yuji] Todo!
Stay back, Brother!
Its cursed energy
output is strong!
[Hanami] Yes, but
it will still be easy
for you to avoid
with your technique.
So what shall I do?
Domain Ex-
(explosion booming)
(gasping) It's a veil!
(Todo grunting)
(air whistling)
(energetic electric
guitar music)
(energy crackling)
(Juzou grunting)
Ah, I see!
I wondered why he sounded
so good without the amp.
It's because this old
man himself is the amp!
His technique amplifies
the tune he plays
and launches it
as cursed energy.
But he's a predictable
mid-range fighter,
it's obvious he doesn't
want me getting close to him.
(air whooshing)
Let's make a wallet!
A wallet full of
that old man smell!
(tense music)
(fabric fluttering)
(footsteps thudding)
Roger that.
Keep going, Nishimiya,
and head to Shouko.
(footsteps thudding)
It's okay, Mei has eyes on Miwa.
(air whooshing)
Good thing the veil
didn't cut off my reception,
but I guess that's because
of who the veil was aimed at.
But I'm afraid we have a spy.
Someone's working with
a curse or a curse user.
[Utahime] Looks like
he was right about that.
-Huh?
-(sword whooshing)
Huh?
I thought I cut you
for sure with that one.
[Utahime] A human?
A curse user?
(Haruta sighing)
Always the same old problem.
(energy warbling)
This is nice, isn't it?
Juzou Kumiya made it for me.
I think you met him him earlier.
Your right hand
isn't very strong,
so let the sword's
hand hold yours.
(Haruta chuckling)
(Utahime grunting)
[Haruta] Hm, so what'll
you give me, lady?
[Nobara] I'll bet all the
girls hate you, don't they?
[Haruta] Hm?
Here you meet someone new
and all you do is
talk about yourself!
I'm gonna charge you.
What makes you think
you're a good enough listener
to charge anyone
money for doing it?
(Nobara growling)
Give it a rest!
[Nobara] You always do
this! You pick the worst times
-to start these arguments!
-Hm?
Ah! (laughing)
Wow, who knew I was so popular?
Look at all these
girls, so awesome!
Weren't you listening
to me just a minute ago?
No sweat, I'll cover you.
Careful not to get
caught in the crossfire.
Be careful where you aim!
-(both gasping)
-(air whooshing)
(veil trickling)
The veil's been lifted!
No way!
It hasn't even been
30 minutes yet!
Time to run!
(footsteps thudding)
What was his deal?
So weird.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
If it isn't my slick new coat
rack floating right up there!
(tense pensive music)
So where should I start?
[Yuji] Huh?
(Hanami grunting)
[Hanami] Looks like
this is as far as we go.
Huh?
Gojo, is that you?
(energy whooshing)
Yuji's on a much higher
level than he was before.
Ah, I see!
Aoi!
Of course he'd be a
great match for Yuji.
Looks like they're
fighting the special-grade,
but I shouldn't have to
worry about them now.
Which means my
priority should be
(air whooshing)
-Hey, you there!
-Hm?
(Juzou laughing)
Coat rack, coat rack, coat rack!
Don't kill him!
(Juzou yelping)
(Juzou grunting)
(stones crashing)
(Juzou groaning)
We have a lot of questions
we need to ask this guy.
Don't let him die on us.
Go on, treat him.
(Yoshinobu growling)
(Gojo gasping)
The guy who was with
Utahime has disappeared.
Guess he must've found
some means of escape.
(air whooshing)
So that just leaves that one.
One adept at running, too.
It's some distance from Yuji.
Oh, well.
Guess I can play a little rough.
Technique Amplification: Blue.
Technique Reversal: Red.
[Hanami] I'm withdrawing.
I'm not arrogant enough to
think I can face Satoru Gojo.
What the hell?
What were you all
trying to do here anyway?
Wait, hold it, Brother!
Why are you stopping me, Todo?
Don't take another step forward,
(energy ringing)
or you'll get caught in it.
(energetic music)
[Gojo] Hollow
(energy booming)
Purple!
(Hanami yelping)
(Yuji grunting)
(Todo chuckling)
He's just as
nonstandard as ever.
(Yuji moaning in awe)
And now we can't tell
if the special-grade
was exorcized or not.
(Juzou wailing)
It hurts!
-It hurts!
-Quiet!
Yay!
That should settle everything!
Or maybe it won't.
(tense music)
(footsteps thudding)
I wonder if Hanami's safe.
Mission accomplished either way.
(closing theme music)
(singer singing in Japanese)
[All] Juju Stroll
[Toge] Salmon.
-(dog barking)
-(cat meowing)
Am I a dog?
No, maybe I like cats.
Although, maybe
if it's a big dog!
All dog.
I think a dog person?
What, really?
No, cats are better!
[Toge] Salmon.
The answer is obviously pandas!
What, you want
me to kill you all?
(Panda roaring)
Everybody hates me, don't they?
I knew it, you all hate me!
Well, there were
only two choices.
Ah, leave it.
(energetic metal music)